Open the practice files folder in the library window.
Find the C.Details.C.EditRibbon file.
Drag it to the 2D or 3D window in the T-shirt wrap folder.
In the 3D T-shirt wrap folder, select the display arrangement point.
Place the ribbon on the arrangement point.
In the purple wrap folder arranged by the attribute editor, adjust the version location.
Use the free sewing line tool to mix the ribbon with the sleeve.
Use the full ribbon tool to make the fold lines on the side of the ribbon.
Select the fold arrangement tool in the 3D tool list.
Click on the newly created fold line.
A fold arrangement location tool appears.
Use the arrow for half fold the ribbon.
This is how to make the fold arrangement tool.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the pattern on both sides of the top and bottom.
In the attribute editor, change the sewing line type to TEND.
After simulation, the pattern will be more even.
Use the editor tool to choose the newly created inner line.
In the attribute editor, adjust the folding angle to 0 degrees.
Activate simulation.
Apply the settings to 3D clothing.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the pattern on both sides of the top and bottom.
Activate simulation.
Enter the drawing window.
Double-click on the Fabric file.
Press and hold the Ripe 2x2 on the file and move the mouse.
Loosen the mouse on the pattern on the 2D or 3D window pattern.
Apply the material to the pattern.
Activate simulation.
Apply the settings to the 3D window.
In the 2D window, use the adjustment panel tool.
Select the heavy pattern.
Press and hold the Ripe 2x2 on the Fabric file.
Align the pattern and copy it.
In the 3D window, use the positioning tool.
Move the pattern to the model wrist.
Use the line sewing tool to sew the pattern on the sleeve.
Activate simulation.
Use the line sewing tool to add the pattern to the supports.
In the 3D window, use the measurement tool to add the pattern to the supports.
Excellent!
Cassie, the checkmark on the top of the skirt is the correct one.
Open the 3D window.
Click the execution button toview.
After the selection is complete, go to thePSAA.
Click the execution button.
Open the 3D window.